and I like the police a lot of comics
talk about them I think they do a fine
job one of my favorite shows is cops
comes on Saturday nights on the Fox
network they were filming it live last
week in my hometown I was watching it
and all of a sudden my front door got
kicked
in all I saw was the back of my head on
my
TV I know that
dude what are you going to do when they
come for you I'll run like the wind
actually not that I would have to run
have you all seen some of these cops
that are on that
show okay look I'm not saying these boys
are out of shape but if you're on a foot
chase and the camera man passes
you you might want to jump up on a
Nordic Track that's all I'm saying drop
the donut and
Jog roll the donut and Chase
it